watchyourtvshowsnow.com 2015-04-25

# Privacy Policy | WatchYourTVShowsNow.com

**Privacy Policy**  
This website, WatchYourTVShowsNow.com (the "Site") is owned and operated by Aragon Advertising Ltd. ("us," "we," or "Company"). We created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain how we use the information we collect on the Site. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

**Information We Collect**  
We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: 1) IP addresses; 2) domain servers; 3) types of computers accessing the Site; and 4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We also use "cookies" to customize content specific to your interests.  
We enable you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes your name and email address. If you communicate with us (for example, by posting on our blog), any information provided in such communication is collected as Personal Information.

**Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**  
We may also (and you authorize us to) disclose your personal information to: a) comply with a court order or other legal process or inquiry; b) protect our rights or property; or c) enforce our Terms of Use. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by unauthorized third parties.  
The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in our blog becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.  
This Site is directed at teenagers and adults not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.  
We have implemented a number of security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse or modification of information we've collected from you. Your personal information is transmitted to and stored on servers that we have taken steps to protect from unauthorized access or intrusion. We do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk.  
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. If we make material changes to the manner in which we handle your personal information, we will notify you in advance of the new policy taking effect so that you have an opportunity to review and consent to the new terms.  
This site is owned and operated by Aragon Advertising, Ltd., 35 Brisbane Road, Ilford, Essex, United Kingdom, IG1 4SP.  
Effective Date: 12/1/2012

This website uses remarketing service to advertise on third party websites to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertiser to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example downloading and installing the toolbar on Firefox or Internet Explorer or the extension on Chrome. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including google use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s pas visits to the watchyourtvshowsnow.com website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

**Contacting Us**   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Aragon Advertising Limited __  
35 Brisbane Road __  
Ilford, Essex, UK, IG1 4SP
